A Guide to the American Society of International Law records, Howard M. Holtzmann papers FA1872
Rockefeller Archive Center
- United Nations Commission on International Trade Law, 1974-2011; IV; 18.42 Cubic Feet 37 legal document boxes and 1 oversize flat box
  - United Nations General Assembly, 35th Session, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Fifth, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Sixth, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 12, Box 89, Folder 1)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Eighth, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 2-9, Box 31, Folder 4)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Ninth, 1976 (Box 89, Folder 10-15, Box 90, Folder 1-15)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Twelfth, 1979-1980 (Box 90, Folder 16-18, Box 91, Folder 1)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Thirteenth, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 2-5)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Fourteenth, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Fifteenth, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Twenty-Sixth, 1993 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Twenty-Seventh, 1994 (Box 91, Folder 9-10)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Twenty-Eighth, 1995 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Thirty-Second, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 2-3)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Thirty-Third, 2000 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Thirty-Fourth, 2001 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Thirty-Fifth, 2001-2002 (Box 92, Folder 6-7, Box 31, Folder 5, Box 93, Folder 1-2)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Thirty-Sixth, 2003 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Thirty-Seventh, 2004 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Thirty-Eighth, 2005 (Box 93, Folder 5, Box 31, Folder 6)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Thirty-Ninth, 2006 (Box 93, Folder 6, Box 94, Folder 1)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Forty-First, 2008 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - 41st-48th, 2008 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Forty-Second, 2009 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Forty-Third, 2010 (Box 94, Folder 5-6)
  - UNCITRAL Sessions - Forty-Fourth, 2011 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Uniform Conciliation Act - I, 2003 (Box 95, Folder 2-4)
  - Uniform Conciliation Act - II - National Conference on Commissioners on Uniform State Laws, 1996-2002 (Box 95, Folder 5-6)
  - Uniform Mediation Act, 2000-2001 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - US Enactment of UNCITRAL Model Laws, 1991-1996 (Box 96, Folder 2-3)
  - Warsaw Conference, 1980 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - "Arbitration and Conciliation, 2000-Present", 2003 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Travaux preparatoires - Amendments Adopted in 2006, Vol 1 - Working Group II Documents (Box 96, Folder 6-7)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 2, 1981 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 32, 2000 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 33, 2000 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 34, 2001 (Box 97, Folder 4-5)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 35, 2001 (Box 97, Folder 6-7)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 36, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 1-3)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 37, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 4-5)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 38-41, 2004-2008 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 39, 2003 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 40, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 41, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 42, 2005 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 43, 2005 (Box 98, Folder 11, Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 44, 2006 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 45, 2006 (Box 99, Folder 3-5)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 46, 2007 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 47, 2007 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 48, 2008 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 49, 2008 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 50, 2009 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 51, 2009 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Working Group on Arbitration - Sessions - 52, 2010 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Working Plan for the Implementation of the SECI Arbitration Project, 2000 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Written Form - Reports, 2005 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Written Form - Supporting Material, 2006 (Box 100, Folder 4)
- American Arbitration Association, 1968-2012; V; 1.88 Cubic Feet 4 legal document boxes
  Biographical / Historical
  The American Arbitration Association (AAA) is a non-profit organization in the field of alternative dispute resolution, providing services to individuals and organizations who wish to resolve conflicts out of court.
  This series contains material created by Holtzmann as part of the governance of the AAA, as well as arbitration proceedings under its auspices. Materials include executive committee meeting minutes and notes, model clauses and decisions for various cases, conference information and publications, research materials, and correspondence.
  Alphabetical by function and record type.
  - 1992 Clause - Russian Federation to AAA Agreement Letter, 1976 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Annual Dinner, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - CCPIT Visit to Stockholm Chamber of Commerce, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Center for Dispute Settlement, 1968-1969 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Comments on Developing Procedures for Emergency Measures, undated (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Commercial Arbitration Rules, 1988 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Corporate Counsel Committee Bulletin, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1973 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - East Europe Model Clauses, 1985-1991 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - General Counsel's 1981 Annual Legal Report (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Germany-Austria, 1990 (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Health Field - "Requests for Grants, re: Dispute Prevention, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - International Arbitration Rules, 1996 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Ludlum Hospital Arbitration in LA, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Meetings - AAA Committee on UNCITRAL Model Law, 1994 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Meetings - Annual Meeting, 1969; 1973 (Box 101, Folder 4, 4A)
  - Meetings - Corporate Counsel Committee Minutes, 1994; 1997 (Box 101, Folder 5-6)
  - Meetings - Executive Committee, 1969; 1973; 1981 (Box 101, Folder 7-22)
  - Meetings - Nominating Committee, 1973 (Box 101, Folder 23)
  - Meetings - Pharmaceutical Industry Luncheon - March 1, 1973 - HMH Speaker on Program, 1973 March 1 (Box 101, Folder 24)
  - Meetings - Subcommittee on International Arbitration Programs Meeting, 1973 October 24 (Box 101, Folder 25)
  - Memos, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Optional Arbitration Clause for Use in Contracts in USA-USSR Trade, 1977 (Box 102, Folder 2-3)
  - Parliamentary Procedure Project, 1968 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials - Basic Documents on International Commercial Arbitration, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials - Board of Directors Guide, 2005-2006 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials - International Rules Procedures - Miscellaneous Rule - A-Z and Code of Ethics, 1977-1997 (Box 102, Folder 7-9)
  - Printed Materials - President's Letter and Financial Statements, 2012 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials - Public Service at the AAA, 2004 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Printed Materials - Agreements, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials - Rules - Assorted, 1987-1998 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - A Proposal for the Fund for the City of New York, 1973 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Regional Directors Conference, 1973 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Report of Commercial Arbitration Committee to 1977 Mid-Winter Meeting of Council of Section of Corporation, Banking and Business Law American Bar Association (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Russian Chamber, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Sylvan Gotshal Award, 1973 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Task Force Commentary, undated (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - UNCITRAL Arbitration Rules, 1979-1981 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Visit by Messrs Ren Jianxin and Tang Houzhi of CCPIT to NY, 1981 (Box 103, Folder 10)
- Arbitration, 1973-2013; VI; 8.06 Cubic Feet 15 legal document boxes and 1 oversize flat box
  Judge Holtzmann also practice widely in the field of arbitration. This series consists of material relating to many of these cases and clients. Materials include written discussions of the cases, drafts and final versions of arbitration rulings, correspondence regarding these cases, and research material.
  - ACPIL - Secretary of State's Advisory Committee on Private International Law, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Africa, undated (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - ALI-ABA International Arbitration Course of Study, undated (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Andrea Giardina - Research Notes, undated (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - AOT Ltd v. Hanwha, 1996-1997 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Asia, 1999 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Australia, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Arbitration Reference Binder, 1997-1998 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Bahrain Matters, 1995-1996 (Box 104, Folder 8-9)
  - Bengt Broms - Research Notes, undated (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Bermuda, 1992-1993 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Bills, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Bokius Matter, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Bosnia Matters, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - British Columbia, 1986-1995 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - British Gas vs. Grynberg, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - British Gas - Opinion Letter, undated (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Charles Allen Jr. Estate, 1990-1995 (Box 105, Folder 8-11)
  - The Chartered Institute of Arbitrators, 1996 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - China - General, 1997 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - China - Arbitration Law, 1997-2003 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - China - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - China - First Mission, American Arbitration Association - Itinerary, undated (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - China - First Mission, American Arbitration Association - AAA Visit to FTAC of the Peoples Republic of China - Trip Report, 1975 January 16-28 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - China - First Mission, American Arbitration Association - Application of the UNIDROIT Principles, 1996 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - China - First Mission, American Arbitration Association - China Delegation to the US, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - China - First Mission, American Arbitration Association - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - China - First Mission, American Arbitration Association - Memorandum to CCPIT, undated (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - China - First Mission, American Arbitration Association - Notebooks, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - China - First Mission, American Arbitration Association - Photographs, undated (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - China - First Mission, American Arbitration Association - Printed Material - Background Material, 1973-1976 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - China - First Mission, American Arbitration Association - Writings, Lectures, Talks, 1975-1982 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - China - Letters of Appointment, 1994-2001 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - China - A New Look at Resolving Disputes in US-China Trade, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - China - Research Material, 1997-2004 (Box 107, Folder 3-4)
  - CIETAC - Cases, 1997-1999 (Box 107, Folder 5-7)
  - CIM Computer/China, 1997 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - CITIC, 1997-1998 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Confidentiality, 1999 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1996-2011 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Dabhol Power v The State of Maharashtra, 1996 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Dictionaries and Ethics of Arbitration, 2013 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Discovery, undated (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Dissents, 1999 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Enron, 1995-1997 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Eritrea-Ethiopia Claims Commission, 2003 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Framing Sekolee Resolutions, 2008 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Gaya - Research Notes, 1988 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - General Arbitration Guidelines, 1988-1996 (Box 108, Folder 10-11)
  - Hong Kong, undated (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Hungary, undated (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - IACAC Arbitration Rules, 1997-2000 (Box 108, Folder 14-15, Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Indian Materials, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Intellectual Property, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - International Arbitration Activities - Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - International Arbitrators 1 - US Arbitration Act Amendments, 1981-1988 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - International Commercial Arbitration - Reference Cards, undated (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Investment Arbitration and the Energy Charter Treaty Conference, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 7-8)
  - Iraq War Claims - Gulf War Claims Reporter, 1994 (Box 109, Folder 9, Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Iraq War Claims - UN-Iraq Arbitration Commission, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Iraq War Claims - UN-Iraq Compensation Commission, 1992-1999 (Box 110, Folder 3-5)
  - Iraq War Claims - UN-Iraq Enclosure to Letter to Alan Gettner, 1993 February 24 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - K/S Norjarl A/S and Hyundai Heavy Industries Co. Ltd - "Mark's Case" - Background Material, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Lapine Technology Corp v Kyocera Corp., 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - The New LCIA Rules, 1997 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - London Court of Arbitration International Arbitration Rules, 1981 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, 1973-1978 (Box 111, Folder 4-5)
  - Mitsubishi, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Model Arbitration Clause with Hungary - Study of Austrian Arbitration Law, 1979-2005 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Morrison and Foerster Indian Arbitration, 1997-2000 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Mushrif Trading, 1999 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - PepsiCo, 1998-1999 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Photran, 1997 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Printed Material - Offprints, 1990-1997 (Box 112, Folder 4-5)
  - Printed Material - International Arbitration Materials, 1990-1994 (Box 112, Folder 6-7)
  - Printed Material - Reference Material, 1986-2004 (Box 113, Folder 1-3)
  - Resnick Project, 2002-2003 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - RHI vs Bidermann, 1993-1994 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Rules - Various, Country Specific, 1994-1997 (Box 113, Folder 6-7)
  - Salini vs Sudan, 1995 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - South Africa Materials, 1996-1999 (Box 114, Folder 1-2)
  - Stockholm Chamber of Commerce - General, 1992-1999 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Stockholm Chamber of Commerce - Arbitration Institute Rules, 1999 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Stockholm Chamber of Commerce - Correspondence, 1985-2000 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Stockholm Chamber of Commerce - Documents Exchanged Between AAA, USSR, Chamber of Commerce and Industry, and Stockholm Chamber of Commerce, undated (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Stockholm Chamber of Commerce - NNG Closing Statement, 2001 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Stockholm Chamber of Commerce - Preparatory Meeting, 1999-2000 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Stockholm Chamber of Commerce - Sanders First Draft, 2001 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Swiss Arbitration, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Syntex, 1987-1994 (Box 115, Folder 1-4)
  - TIOI-Texaco - NGDU Sutorminskneft - Drafts, 1992 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - TIOI-Texaco - NGDU Sutorminskneft - Extra Blanks, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - TIOI-Texaco - Noyabrsk, OJSC - General, 2000-2001 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - TIOI-Texaco - Noyabrsk, OJSC - Chronological File, 1999-2001 (Box 115, Folder 7-8)
  - TIOI-Texaco - Noyabrsk, OJSC - Claimant Submissions, 2000-2001 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - TIOI-Texaco - Noyabrsk, OJSC - Ernst and Young Experts Review, 2000 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - TIOI-Texaco - Noyabrsk, OJSC - Respondent Submissions, 2000-2001 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - TIOI-Texaco - Noyabrsk, OJSC - Statement Document Joint Binders, 1992-2001 (Box 116, Folder 2-3)
  - TIOI-Texaco - Noyabrsk, OJSC - Statement of Claim, 1999 (Box 116, Folder 4-5)
  - TPIF v Guam Port Authority of Guam and the Property Insurance Facility Limited, 1993-1997 (Box 116, Folder 6, Box 117, Folder 1)
  - US Arbitration Act Amendments, 1987-1992 (Box 117, Folder 2-3)
  - US Law, 1997-2001 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - US State Department Advisory Committee on Private International Law, 1981 (Box 117, Folder 4A)
  - Valticos, 1988 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Vienna, 1980-1981 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Writings - Freshfields Arbitration Lecture, 1989 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Zhuzhou - ZCCW, 1998 (Box 117, Folder 8)
- Organizations, 1957-2010; VII; 7.06 Cubic Feet 15 legal document boxes
  Reflecting the scope of Judge Holtzmann's engagment with the international legal community, this series contains materials pertaining to his work with a wide variety of non-governmental, international governmental, and educational institutions and organizations. Organizations include: the American Bar Association, the Environmental Law Institute, the International Chamber of Commerce, the International Council for Commercial Arbitration, and the Permanent Court of Arbitration. Materials include correspondence, memos and communiques, conference material, meeting minutes, drafts of rules and policy, writings, and research and printed materials.
  Alphabetical by organization.
  - American Bar Association - Model Standards, 2003 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - American Bar Association - Model Standards of Conduct for Mediators, 2003-2005 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - American Bar Association - Report of the Annual Meeting of the Council, 1974 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - American Bar Association - Annual Meeting Program, 1984 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - American Bar Association Annual Meetings - DC - General, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - American Bar Association Annual Meetings - DC - Report of Arbitration Committee, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - American Bar Association Annual Meetings - DC - Writings and Presentations, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - American Bar Association Annual Meetings - San Francisco - General, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 1-2)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - American Bar Association Annual Meetings - San Francisco - Arbitration Committee Meeting, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - American Bar Association Annual Meetings - San Francisco - Arbitration Committee Program - General, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 4-5)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - American Bar Association Annual Meetings - San Francisco - Arrangement Committee Program - HMH Statement, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - American Bar Association Annual Meetings - San Francisco - Bibliographies of Participants, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - American Bar Association Annual Meetings - San Francisco - Council Meeting and HMH Report to Council, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - American Bar Association Annual Meetings - San Francisco - Registration and General, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - American Bar Association Annual Meetings - San Francisco - Minutes of Council Meetings and Annual Section Meeting, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - American Society of International Law - Panel, 1997 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - Association of Arbitrators (Southern Africa) Conference Discussion Paper, 1997 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - Chartered Institute of Arbitrators Millennium Conference, 1999 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - International Arbitration and Comparative Law, 1990 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - International Arbitration Forum, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - International Congress of Arbitration, 1969-1971 (Box 120, Folder 3-4)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - International Commercial Arbitration Course - Dubrovnilk, 2001 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - International Commercial Arbitration and Law Libraries: A View from the Hague, 1994 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - IFCAI - Hong Kong, 1995 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - Iran-UNCITRAL, 1981 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - Multiple Parties, Multiple Problems, 2007 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - NYU Conference on International Courts and Tribunals, 1995 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - NYU Selected Institute on International Law, undated (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - UN Conference on International Commercial Arbitration, 1958 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Conferences and Colloquiums - UNCITRAL 25th Anniversary, 1992 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Law Institute - General, 1994-2000 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Law Institute - Annual Report, 1999 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Law Institute - Board of Directors Meetings, 2000-2005 (Box 121, Folder 7-10)
  - Environmental Law Institute - Correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Law Institute - Development Audit Report, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Law Institute - Opportunities of Advancing Environmental Justice, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - International Chamber of Commerce - General, 1980 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - International Chamber of Commerce - AAA/ICSID - Joint Colloquium, 1997 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - International Chamber of Commerce - Arbitration Rules Revisions and Commission Bureau Meetings, 1995-1997 (Box 122, Folder 6-7)
  - International Chamber of Commerce - Commission on International - General, 1998-2001 (Box 122, Folder 8, Box 123, Folder 1)
  - International Chamber of Commerce - Commission on International Arbitration - Truncated Tribunals, 1997 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - International Chamber of Commerce - IATA Agency - AD Travel Service, 1969 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - International Chamber of Commerce - Printed Material, 1990s (Box 123, Folder 4-7, Box 124, Folder 1)
  - International Chamber of Commerce - Rules - Arbitration Rules, 1996 (Box 124, Folder 1A)
  - International Chamber of Commerce - Rules - Commission on International Arbitration Meeting, 1980 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - International Chamber of Commerce - Rules - Forum on ICC Rules/Court - Report on Confidentiality, 1994-2002 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - International Chamber of Commerce - Rules - Minutes of ICC-AAA Meeting, 1970 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - International Chamber of Commerce - Rules - Parking Liability Rules, 1996 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - International Chamber of Commerce - Rules - Revisions, 1996-1997 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - International Chamber of Commerce - Statement of Purpose and Procedures, 2009 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - International Chamber of Commerce - Symposium on International Arbitration - General, 1970-1971 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - International Chamber of Commerce - Symposium on International Arbitration - Paris Talk, 1970 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - International Chamber of Commerce - Symposium on International Arbitration - Paris Trip Background Material, 1970 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - International Chamber of Commerce - UNIDROIT, 1994-1996 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - International Council for Commercial Arbitration - General, 1994-2002 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - International Council for Commercial Arbitration - Congresses - 12th, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 4-5)
  - International Council for Commercial Arbitration - Congresses - 14th, 1998 (Box 125, Folder 6-7)
  - International Council for Commercial Arbitration - Congresses - 18th, 2006 (Box 126, Folder 1-2)
  - International Council for Commercial Arbitration - Congresses - Seoul, 1996 (Box 126, Folder 3-4)
  - International Council for Commercial Arbitration - Congresses - Paris, 1998 (Box 126, Folder 5-6)
  - International Council for Commercial Arbitration - Congresses - London, 2002 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - International Council for Commercial Arbitration - Congresses - Beijing, 2004 (Box 127, Folder 2)